Hello.
こんにちは
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いね
Hey, you're so cute.
ねえ、すげえ可愛い
Do you like sex?
エッチ好き?
I like sex, but I don't do it much.
エッチは好きだけど、あんまりしないです
Ah, I like it.
あ、好きなんだ
I like it though.
好きだけど
Not very much.
あんましない
I don't have a chance to.
する機会がない
do not have.
ない
No encounters?
出会いがない?
I don't have any meetings and I don't have time.
出会いもないし、時間もない
Don't you have time?
時間もないの?
You'll get picked up, right?
ナンパとかされるでしょ?
Pick up girls sometimes.
ナンパはたまに
Will it be done?
される?
What do you say to me?
なんて声かけられるの?
It's a type.
タイプですって
Isn't it too abrupt?
唐突すぎない?
He says he's the type who suddenly came.
急に来てタイプなんですって
You said you were approached today too, right?
今日もだって声かけられたって言ってたでしょ?
I was told that I am your type again today.
今日もタイプなんですって言われて
Under what circumstances?
どういう状況で?
As I was walking and about to pass through the ticket gate, it suddenly stopped right in front of me.
歩いてて、改札通ろうとしたら、急に目の前で止まって
I'm the type of person who likes to walk a little.
タイプなんですけど、ちょっと歩いて
It's not like I won't say that.
それ言わないんじゃないよ
You'll be surprised if you do that.
したらびっくりしちゃう
I said sorry for leaving in such a short time.
時間ないで行って、すみませんって
You don't usually say that at the ticket gate.
改札でさ、普通言わないじゃん
As much as I want to say it, it really touched my heart, didn't it?
言いたくなるくらい、やっぱり、心に刺さったんじゃね?
I'm happy about that though.
それは嬉しいですけどね
Honestly.
素直に
bothersome?
迷惑?
Because I'm not good at saying no.
断るのが苦手だから
I'm not good at saying no.
断るの苦手なんだ
So, you were picked up and you followed me?
じゃあ、ナンパされて、ついていっちゃったか
I can't keep up, but when we exchange contact information on LINE etc.
ついてはいかないけど、LINEとか連絡先交換しちゃうときは
there is.
あります
I'll teach you.
教 えちゃうんだ
I won't give it back though.
返さないけど
I won't give it back.
返さないんだ
I won't give it back though.
返さないけど
On the spot.
その場ではね
Replace it on the spot and keep it aside.
その場で交換しといて、とっておきます
I see.
なるほどね
nice.
いいね
She's so cute, she really smiles.
可愛いな、本当に笑顔が
It's embarrassing.
照れますね
TRUE?
本当?
That being said.
ここまで言われると
Really cute.
本当に可愛い
I feel like I want to keep an eye on it.
なんか、見押し押ししたくなる
I would like you to do that.
してほしいですよ
thank you.
ありがとう
Well then, I guess you could say I'm having sex by myself.
じゃあ、え、一人でさ、エッチっていうか
Have you ever had sex alone?
一人エッチしたことある?
Yes, but.
ありますけど
Yes, there is.
うん、あるんだ
There is though.
あるけど
Do you usually do that?
するの、普段?
I don't do it very often.
あんまりしないですね
Not much?
あんまりしない?
Yeah.
うん
Don't you want to?
したくならない?
Are you studying?
勉強してる?
Yes, but I haven't.
なるけど、してないですね
It's kind of annoying.
なんか、めんどくさい
Then I wanted to meet someone.
だったら誰かとしたいなって
Uncle, it's better to have an uncle.
おじんちゃん、おじんちゃんがあったほうがいい
oh dear.
まあ
I see.
なるほどね
I'm looking forward to it.
ちょっと、楽しみですね
Well then, let's do some things today.
じゃあ、今日は色々しようね
Are you studying?
勉強してる?
I am doing.
してます
why?
なんで?
I don't do this much, so this is what I do.
あんまりしないから、こういうこと
Like Hamedori?
はめどりみたいな?
Have you never done it?
したことない?
I haven't done much.
あんまりしたことない
Ah, I've done that before.
あ、したことあるんだ
Only once.
1回だけ
There is.
あるんだ
How?
どういうふうに?
With my boyfriend, when I put my boyfriend in.
彼氏と、彼氏入れてるときに
Ah, I see.
あー、なるほどね
My boyfriend has it.
彼氏が持ってる
That's it.
それだけ
Is that all?
それだけ?
yes.
はい
It's already soft.
もう柔らかい
it hurts.
痛い
Look at your own face.
見て、自分の顔
Isn't it cute?
かわいいでしょ?
no.
いや
Here, look from below.
こっち、下からしてほら
Peet.
ぺーって
Don't hide your face.
隠さないで、顔
cute.
かわいい
Peet.
ぺーって
difficult.
難しい
difficult?
難 しい?
Where do you touch it?
どこ触るんですか?
In your body.
体の中で
One song.
一首
Is that so?
そうなの?
difficult.
難しい
show me.
見せて
By yourself.
自分で
I'm flipping through it myself.
自分でめくってす
Turn it over properly.
ちゃんとめくって
Ah, amazing.
あー、すごい
Those are beautiful breasts.
綺麗なおっぱいだね
Ah, nice.
あー、いいね
nice.
いいね
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっと 立ってみて
Try putting your breasts closer together.
おっぱい寄せてみてよ
Shut up.
き ゅーっと
Submit.
寄 せる
Ah, amazing.
あー、すごい
Why are you hiding your face?
なんで顔隠してんの?
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
I'm twitching.
ぴくんとしてる
Hurray for a moment, with both hands.
ちょっと万歳してよ、両手で
I don't like it, it's just not good.
嫌だ、ちょっとダメ
Really.
本当に
why?
なんで?
Really without it.
本当に無しで
I really wish I could do without it.
本当に無しでお願いしたい
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
for a moment.
一瞬
You're showing it to me now.
今見せてくれてるじゃん
No more.
もうダメ
why?
なんで?
Really.
本当に
Is it unprocessed?
未処理なの?
There's no way it's unprocessed.
未処理ってわけない
I'm asking you some questions though.
雑問は言ってますけどな
But I don't like it, because I kind of forgot about it.
でも嫌だ、ちょっと忘れてたから
I haven't even checked.
確認すらしてないから
Then show me.
じゃあ見せてくれ
This one isn't even finished yet.
こっちも途中終わってない
I got wet.
てか濡れちゃった
picture?
え?
what?
なに?
I got wet.
濡れちゃった
Are you going to make it that bright?
そんな明るくするんですか?
Even when I take pictures there.
そこ撮るときも
It's impossible, right?
無理だよ、じゃん
fault.
あら
Really.
本当に
Get a little excited.
ちょっと気上がって
Take it out and open it.
出し開いて
Like now.
今みたいに
yes.
そう
Are you excited?
興奮しちゃったの?
Yeah.
うん
I just tried to touch it.
触ろうとしただけで
Being touched.
触られる
Yeah, I like it.
うん、好きだよ
cold.
寒い
yeah?
ん?
It's a little good.
ちょっといいじゃん
I like it.
好きだよ
picture?
え?
like?
好き?
picture?
え?
Go here too.
こっちも行って
Yeah.
うん
Go.
行って
Ah, amazing.
あー、すごい
Put your hands on me and stick your butt out.
手について、こっちのお尻を突き出して
Ah, that's right.
あー、そうだ
Beautiful.
綺麗な
Take a look here too.
こっちも見てごらん
Those are beautiful feet.
綺麗な足だね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's really tight.
すごい締めてる
yeah?
ん?
Knees, knees.
膝、膝
Knees, knees, knees.
膝、膝、膝
amazing.
すごい
Look at me again.
またこっち向いて
copper?
どう?
I love it, that's what it is.
好きだよ、そんなの
Let's get it out.
出しちゃおう
Try sticking it out.
グーッと突き出してごらん
No?
やだ?
Yeah.
うん
I'm sleeping a lot, there's something wrong with that.
すごい寝てる、なんかある
Hey, go over here too.
ね、こっちも行ってごらん
Look.
ほ ら
No, really no.
やだ、本当にやだ
No.
ダメ
Well then, go here too.
じゃあ、こっちも行って
It's really difficult.
本当に難しい
hard.
辛い
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロい
It's so beautiful.
すっごい綺麗だ
You're clean shaven.
綺麗に剃ってるね
Do it yourself, with both hands, open your pussy.
自分でさ、両手でさ、おまんこ開いて
It's amazing how you fall.
倒れちゃうの、すごい
What, what are you going to do?
え、どうすんの?
Open your pussy.
おまんこ開いて
like this?
こう?
yes.
そう
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, you can lie down there.
じゃあ、そこ、横になっちゃっていいよ
Open your pussy.
おまんこ開けてごらん
Erotic.
エロい
Oh, I'll hide it.
あ、隠しちゃう
I'll hide it.
隠しちゃう
Oh, that's amazing.
おー、すごい
tight.
きつい
It's really tight.
すっごい締まるね
Are you tightening it?
締めてる?
now.
今
Be selfish.
勝手になる
It's really tight.
すっごい締まる
Is it tightening on its own?
勝手に締まってんの?
this.
これ
I'm putting in a lot of effort.
力入っちゃう
That's right.
そうなんだ
What do you like?
どこが好き?
Oh, it's so tight.
おー、すっごい締まる
oh.
おー
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Awesome.
す っごい
Can it happen again?
またなっちゃっていい?
While looking at me.
こっち見ながら
You're good at it.
上手だね
Lie down for a while.
ちょっと横になって
here?
ここ?
Oh, I guess I'll give you a butt.
あ、お尻付けしちゃうか
Looks good.
上手そう
Look here.
こっち見て
So beautiful.
すっごい綺麗
Oh, it's really tight.
お ー、すっごい締まる
That's a beautiful butt.
綺麗なお尻だね
Oh, that's amazing.
お、すごい
Water came out.
水が出てきた
It's here.
ここだ
It's coming out.
出てくるね
beautiful.
綺麗
sorry.
ごめんなさい
why?
なんで?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
please.
お願いします
Eh, why?
え、なんで?
No?
ダメ?
do?
する?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
It's been a while since I rinsed the baby.
おむすのすすぎ、久しぶりなんだけど
Because I did.
したからね
Because I ate it.
おむしたからね
copper?
どう?
Please turn this way.
こっち向いてください
Please put your butt on.
お尻付きだしてください
Ah, amazing.
あ、 すごい
Will it become?
なっていっちゃうの?
Will it come out?
抜ける?
Ah, there you go.
あ、やっば
Ah, here it is.
あ、やっばこれ
Please move.
動いてください
Look.
ほ ら
Hold my hand.
手をついてさ
Raise your legs.
脚を上げて
Please move once.
一回動いてください
動
Please stay.
いて ください
Move.
動 いて
Please turn in the same direction.
同じ方向になってください
yeah?
ん?
Next to you?
横に?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Normally.
普通に
Drop your legs.
脚を落としてください
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
Please take a break.
休憩してください
Strange story.
変な話